isparkmedia.com 2011-11-27

# Privacy Policy | iSpark Media

**1\. Our Commitment to Privacy**

Your privacy is important to iSpark Media, Inc. (the “Company”). This Privacy Policy lets you know how we handle personally identifiable information such as name, email address, or other contact information (“Personal Information”) you may share with the Company through “www.isparkmedia.com” (the “Site”). Some websites of our affiliated companies have their own privacy policies, which may be accessed at the websites for those affiliates. 

We provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**2\. Scope**

This Privacy Policy explains how we handle Personal Information you share with the Company, as well as aggregated and/or anonymous user information that does not contain Personal Information. 

**3\. Personal Information Collection**

You may use this Site to learn about our company without disclosing any Personal Information. There may be times when we ask you to provide us with Personal Information. For example, we may ask for your Personal Information in order for us to provide you with information you request, such as press releases or other investor information. We may ask for contact information such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number. We may also collect your email address if you send us an email request for information. We may retain your Personal Information for purposes of future communications. 

**4\. Uses of Information**

We may use Personal Information and aggregated and/or anonymous user information in the following ways: 

  * for the purposes for which you specifically provided the Personal Information, such as sending you information about our company;
  * to answer emails we receive from you;
  * to enhance existing features of this Site or assist us in developing new features;
  * to provide our affiliated companies with information about our user base and website usage patterns; and
  * to allow us to personalize the content that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences.

In addition, we may share your Personal Information and aggregated and/or anonymous user information as follows: 

  * with our affiliated companies;
  * with our suppliers for the purpose of providing services for us (for example, mailing information in response to your request for information); and
  * as required by law, in conjunction with a government inquiry, or in litigation or dispute resolution.

Furthermore, in the case of any significant transaction or event involving the Company or any of its related entities or divisions such as, by way of example, a sale, merger, amalgamation, financing, re-organization, liquidation, or insolvency, other parties to the transaction and their professional advisors may need to have access to customer lists and various databases which include Personal Information as part of the due diligence process. In this event, the Company would only provide such access under terms of a strict confidentiality agreement. Also, upon completion of the transaction or event, your Personal Information may be transferred to the Company’s (or its related entity’s) successor-in-interest to be used for the purposes for which it was collected. 

**5\. Cookies**

We may use cookie technology and other tracking devices on our Site. A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a website and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer’s memory. When you arrive at our Site or take advantage of key features, we may pass cookies to your computer. The use of cookies allows us to measure Site activity to provide a better user experience. Cookies and other tracking devices may be used to tell us the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our Site, the site you visited just before coming to ours, and the name of your Internet service provider. 

You may elect to refuse cookies. Please refer to your Internet browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies and how to manage their use. It is possible, however, that some parts of our Site will not work properly if cookies are disabled. 

**6\. Outside Links**

Our Site may contain links to third-party websites not controlled by the Company or covered by this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy statement of other sites you visit before providing any Personal Information. 

**7\. Information Security**

To prevent unauthorized access and to maintain data accuracy, we use reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

The Company recognizes the importance of safeguarding Personal Information in the Company’s possession from theft, inappropriate use or improper distribution. It should, however, be recognized that no company can perfectly protect Personal Information. 

**8\. Privacy Inquiries**

If you have any concerns or questions regarding our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at support@isparkmedia.com. 

**9\. Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

We do not collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Site is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**10\. How You Can Access or Modify Your Information or Choices**

If we have used your Personal Information to send you information, you can request to no longer receive information from us by emailing a request to support@isparkmedia.com. 

You can correct factual errors in your Personal Information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections. 

**11\. For Users Outside of the United States**

****This Site is operated in the United States. Any Personal Information provided to us will be transferred to the United States, and by using this Site and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to this transfer. ****

**12\. Policy Modifications**

We retain the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. The date on which the Privacy Policy was last updated will appear at the top of this Privacy Policy.
